Unterberger, S. Herbert Arbitration and Research Files 5636
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Wallerstein Company - Yarway Corporation (Box 36)
  - WPHL, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Yarway, 1968-1980 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Yarway, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Seniority and Classification Panels, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Bound volumes of Arbitration Decisions, plus card index (decisions only) in chronological order. (Box 36A)
  - Arbitration, 1965-1966 (Box 36A, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration, 1965 (Box 36A, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration, 1962-1964 (Box 36A, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration, 1961-1962 (Box 36A, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration, 1957-1959 (Box 36A, Folder 5)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Bound volumes of Arbitration Decisions, plus card index (decisions only) in chronological order. (Box 36B)
  - Arbitration, 1979 (Box 36B, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration, July - December 1975 (Box 36B, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration, 1977-1978 (Box 36B, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Decision, 1977 (Box 36B, Folder 4)
  - July - Dec. 1978 (Box 36B, Folder 5)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Bound volumes of Arbitration Decisions, plus card index (decisions only) in chronological order. (Box 36C)
  - Note Cards, 1966-1972 (Box 36C, Folder 1)
  - 1967 Arbitrations, 1966-1967 (Box 36C, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration, 1967 (Box 36C, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration, 1969 (Box 36C, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration, 1970 (Box 36C, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration, 1972 (Box 36C, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration, 1971 (Box 36C, Folder 7)
- Studies: American Bar Association Study (Box 37)
  - ABA Study (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Herbert Unterberg, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Statistical Package for the Social Sciences-, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Statistical Package for Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Statistical Package for Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Statistical Package for Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Statistical Package for Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Statistical Package for Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Statistical Package for Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Studies: American Bar - Federal Reserve Bank (Box 38)
  - ALI-ABA, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - American Law Institute, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Statistical Analysis of Wage Structures in Three Federal Reserve Banks - Jacob De Rooy, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Boston, 1960-1968 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland, 1962-1966 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Kansas City (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Report on Study of Salary Structures, Job Evaluation Programs and Related Matters of the Federal Reserve Banks (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Federal Reserve Banks Execs., 1946 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Federal Banks, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Boston Federal Bank (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Job Evaluation Manual (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Studies: Federal Reserve Bank - Hospital Study (Box 39)
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute For Cancer Research, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - O.E.I.U. Work, 1950-1952 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Clerical, Administrative and Technical Jobs, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - S. Herbert Unterberger, 1964-1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Job Evaluation Manual Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Confidential, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Cole and Associates, Inc. General Report - Bank Officer Salary Survey, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Montelefore Report, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Studies: Hospital Study (Box 40)
  - N.Y. Hospitals, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Hospitals, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - The Mount Sinai Hospital Wage and Salary Administration Manual, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Studies: Hospital Study - Star Metal (Box 41)
  - Montefere, 1961-1968 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Hudson Tire, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - International Latex, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Lever Brothers, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Printing Industry of America, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Employee Retirement Fund IPP and AU of NA, 1955-1958 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Swedish Civil Servants, 1958-1971 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - New York City, 1968-1971 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Star Metal, 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous: Research Files (Box 42)
  - Arcwire-Morgan Contract Job Descriptions and Evaluations, 1968-1971 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Carol Anne Corp., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Knox Glass Co., 1964 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Gold, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, 1937-1968 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - GBBA, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous: Mostly job evaluation manuals (Box 43)
  - OEIU - Job Evaluations, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Evaluation Manual Hourly Jobs Section 1 Guide for Describing and Evaluating - Corning Glass Works, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Job Ranking Manual October 1962 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Job Evaluation Committee, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Job Evaluation, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Job Evaluation Plan for Productions and Related Jobs, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Job Evaluation Plan for Production and Related Jobs, 1937-1949 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Job Rating Manual (Shop), 1954 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Job Evaluation Plan for Production and Related Jobs, 1937-1949 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Job Ranking Manual Pottery Plants American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp., 1960 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Ingrade Wage-Rate Progression in War and Peace, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Wayne State University Self-Study, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Hayes Association Seminar, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous: Mostly job evaluation manuals (Box 44)
  - Wallerstein Co. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Hourly Job Rating Plan (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Manual Job Evaluation Supplementary Booklet, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Job Descriptions and Evaluations, 1941-1959 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Job Evaluation, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Job Rating Manual, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Job Evaluation Plant Jobs Reading Metals Refining Corp. As of 12/1/61 Contract, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Time Study Training Manual, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Wallerstein Company Inc. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Wallerstein Company, Inc. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation Manual Hourly Jobs Section 2, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Veeder-Root Job Evaluation Manual, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Wallerstein Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Position Classification and Pay Plan, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Job Evaluation Manual, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Guide for Use of Nema Job Rating Manual, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Job Evaluation Manual (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Standard Data Process and Industrial Engineering Department, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Evaluation Manual Hourly Jobs Section 2, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Evaluation Manual Hourly Jobs Section 1, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Job Evaluation Manual (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Supervisory Job Evaluation Manual, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Job Evaluation Study, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Job Rating Specifications, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- [This box has not been inventoried] (Box 45)
  - Arbitration - The Fraternal Order of Police -and- The Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - National Joint Board Settlement of Jurisdictional Disputes, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Serice Segment Data Domestic - Com Master - originally in box 9 (Box 46)